ZULLY BARRIENTOS

Product and design professional with 5 years of experience across UI/UX design, program and project management and research. I excel at collaborating with diverse stakeholders and working through the knots of the end-to-end product design process including: requirements gathering, user research, information architecture, content strategy, wireframing, prototyping, development and testing.

TOOLS

Azure DevOps

InDesign

Illustrator

Photoshop

Adobe XD

Sketch

Figma

InVision

MyBalsamiq

GitHub

Visio

Usability Hub

LANGUAGES

CSS3

HTML5

JavaScript

English

Spanish

Portuguese

SKILLS

Product Management

UI/UX Design

User Research

Info. Architecture

Wireframing

Prototyping

Testing

Front End Dev.

Writing

Illustration

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

MICROSOFT | Redmond, WA

Xbox Live Program Manager, Apr. 2019 – Present

- Conducted user research and market analysis to identify feature/functional requirements for a new Xbox parental controls mobile app
- Created information architecture design and wireframing for entire app

BEAUTY BAKERIE | San Diego, CA

Digital Product Designer, Oct. 2018 - Feb. 2019

• Helped increase online conversion by creating playful yet polished email and web campaigns as well as experimental landing pages to highlight UGC

AGUILAR CASTILLO LOVE | San José, Costa Rica

Web Designer & Brand Consultant, Dec. 2017 - Oct. 2018

- · Led brand identity and content development for print and web
- Executed the design of a custom responsive website using WordPress

BLOC | Remote

UI/UX & Front End Development Apprentice, Oct. 2017 - May 2019

• Apprenticeship to update my skillset in the areas of: user research, info. architecture, visual design, prototyping, testing & front end build

M POWERED STRATEGIES, INC. | Washington, D.C.

IT Project Manager & Graphic Designer, Oct. 2014 – Oct. 2017

- Lead for the firm's rebranding project; included overhaul of company's visual identity, corporate messaging and a new responsive website
- Redesigned waterfall SDLC processes into agile methodology for all IT projects across the Department of Veterans Affairs' (VA) IT office (OI&T)

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, SAN DIEGO | La Jolla, CA

Master of Public Policy and Management, 2014

AMHERST COLLEGE | Amherst, MA

Bachelor of Art & Art History, 2011